{
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Man Out of Time'?",
            "answer": "Captain America",
            "options": ["Captain America", "Iron Man", "Hulk", "Thor"]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Who is the God of Thunder?",
            "answer": "Thor",
            "options": ["Thor", "Loki", "Black Panther", "Wolverine"]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Which character has a retractable adamantium skeleton?",
            "answer": "Wolverine",
            "options": ["Wolverine", "Cyclops", "Storm", "Doctor Strange"]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Who is the web-slinging superhero from New York City?",
            "answer": "Spider Man ",
            "options": ["Spider Man ", "Daredevil", "Moon Knight", "Blade"]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Which character is known for her agility and stealth abilities?",
            "answer": "Black Widow",
            "options": ["Black Widow", "She-Hulk", "Medusa", "Elektra"]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Who is the Prince of Lies?",
            "answer": "Loki",
            "options": ["Loki", "Thanos", "Magneto", "Ultron"]
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Which character can control the weather?",
            "answer": "Storm",
            "options": ["Storm", "Jean Grey", "Ms. Marvel ", "Invisible Woman"]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Who is the Sorcerer Supreme?",
            "answer": "Doctor Strange",
            "options": ["Doctor Strange", "Mordo", "Ancient One", "Silver Surfer"]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Star-Lord'?",
            "answer": "Peter Quill",
            "options": ["Peter Quill", "Rocket Raccoon", "Groot", "Drax"]
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Who is the king of Wakanda?",
            "answer": "Black Panther",
            "options": ["Black Panther", "Storm", "Luke Cage", "Falcon"]
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Which character can absorb and redirect energy?",
            "answer": "Absorbing Man",
            "options": ["Absorbing Man", "Hawkeye", "Punisher", "Ghost Rider"]
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "Who is the ruler of Atlantis?",
            "answer": "Namor",
            "options": ["Namor", "Stingray", "Loa", "Triton"]
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Which character can generate force fields?",
            "answer": "Invisible Woman",
            "options": ["Invisible Woman", "Spectrum", "Crystal", "Magneto"]
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Who is the God of Mischief?",
            "answer": "Loki",
            "options": ["Loki", "Thor", "Odin", "Zeus"]
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Which character can control fire?",
            "answer": "Human Torch",
            "options": ["Human Torch", "Firestar", "Pyro", "Phoenix"]
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "Who is the Master of Magnetism?",
            "answer": "Magneto",
            "options": ["Magneto", "Professor X", "Iceman", "Beast"]
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "Which character can teleport?",
            "answer": "Nightcrawler",
            "options": ["Nightcrawler", "Blink", "Deadpool", "Shadowcat"]
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "Who is the web-slinger's alter ego?",
            "answer": "Peter Parker",
            "options": ["Peter Parker", "Bruce Banner", "Tony Stark", "Steve Rogers"]
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "Which character is known for her ability to manipulate reality?",
            "answer": "Scarlet Witch",
            "options": ["Scarlet Witch", "Jean Grey", "Rogue", "Jubilee"]
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "Who wields the power Cosmic Cube?",
            "answer": "Red Skull",
            "options": ["Red Skull", "Thanos", "Ultron", "Loki"]
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "Which character can stretch his body like rubber?",
            "answer": "Mr. Fantastic",
            "options": ["Mr. Fantastic", "Ultron", "Yondu", "Thing"]
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "Who is the space pirate who becomes a member of the Guardians of the Galaxy?",
            "answer": "Yondu",
            "options": ["Yondu", "Starfox", "Adam Warlock", "Gamora"]
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Kingpin of Crime'?",
            "answer": "Wilson Fisk",
            "options": ["Wilson Fisk", "Otto Octavius", "Mysterio", "Magneto"]
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "Who is the leader of HYDRA?",
            "answer": "Red Skull",
            "options": ["Red Skull", "Nick Fury", "Thanos", "Loki"]
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "Which character can turn into a giant green rage monster?",
            "answer": "Hulk",
            "options": ["Hulk", "Thing", "She-Hulk", "Colossus"]
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "Who is the first Avenger?",
            "answer": "Captain America",
            "options": ["Captain America", "Iron Man", "Thor", "Hulk"]
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "Which character is known for his healing factor?",
            "answer": "Wolverine",
            "options": ["Wolverine", "Deadpool", "Colossus", "Cyclops"]
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "Who is the alien symbiote that bonds with Eddie Brock?",
            "answer": "Venom",
            "options": ["Venom ", "Carnage", "Toxin", "Groot"]
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Man Without Fear'?",
            "answer": "Daredevil",
            "options": ["Daredevil", "Spider Man ", "Hawkeye", "Black Panther"]
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "Which character is known for his ability to manipulate reality?",
            "answer": "Scarlet Witch",
            "options": ["Scarlet Witch", "Quicksilver", "Vision", "Loki"]
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "Which character is known for his time-traveling adventures?",
            "answer": "Cable",
            "options": ["Cable", "Wolverine", "Doctor Strange", "Iron Man"]
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "Which character transforms into a powerful feline warrior?",
            "answer": "Black Cat",
            "options": ["Black Cat", "Black Panther", "Moon Knight", "Werewolf by Night"]
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "question": "Who can shoot energy blasts from his eyes?",
            "answer": "Cyclops",
            "options": ["Cyclops", "Optic", "Starfox", "Blindspot"]
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "question": "Which character can control minds with his telepathic powers?",
            "answer": "Professor X",
            "options": ["Professor X", "Magneto", "Doctor Strange", "Thanos"]
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "question": "Who is the king of Wakanda?",
            "answer": "Black Panther",
            "options": ["Black Panther", "Storm", "Luke Cage", "War Machine"]
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "question": "Who wields the power Cosmic Cube?",
            "answer": "Red Skull",
            "options": ["Red Skull", "Thanos", "Ultron", "Loki"]
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "question": "Which character can transform into a large beast?",
            "answer": "Beast",
            "options": ["Beast", "Hulk", "Colossus", "Thing"]
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "question": "Who can travel through time and space?",
            "answer": "Doctor Strange",
            "options": ["Doctor Strange", "Thanos", "Moon Knight", "Red Skull"]
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "question": "Who is the leader of HYDRA?",
            "answer": "Red Skull",
            "options": ["Red Skull", "Nick Fury", "Thanos", "Loki"]
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "Which character can absorb and redirect energy?",
            "answer": "Absorbing Man",
            "options": ["Absorbing Man", "Hawkeye", "Arrow", "Speedy"]
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "question": "Who is the ruler of Atlantis?",
            "answer": "Namor",
            "options": ["Namor", "Aquaman", "Neptune", "Poseidon"]
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "question": "Which character can generate force fields?",
            "answer": "Invisible Woman",
            "options": ["Invisible Woman", "Forcefield Generator", "Barrier", "Shieldmaster"]
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "question": "Who is the God of Mischief?",
            "answer": "Loki",
            "options": ["Loki", "Thor", "Odin", "Heimdall"]
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "question": "Which character can control fire?",
            "answer": "Human Torch",
            "options": ["Human Torch", "Firestar", "Pyro", "Phoenix"]
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "question": "Who is the mutant with superhuman strength and invulnerability?",
            "answer": "Colossus",
            "options": ["Colossus", "Hulk", "She-Hulk", "Thing"]
        },
        {
            "id": 46,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Master Assassin'?",
            "answer": "Elektra",
            "options": ["Elektra", "Black Widow", "Deadpool", "Moon Knight"]
        },
        {
            "id": 47,
            "question": "Who is the mutant with the power to manipulate probability?",
            "answer": "Longshot",
            "options": ["Longshot", "Wolverine", "Cyclops", "Storm"]
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Prince of Power'?",
            "answer": "Black Bolt",
            "options": ["Black Bolt", "Medusa", "Gorgon", "Karnak"]
        },
        {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "Who is the Asgardian god of war?",
            "answer": "Balder",
            "options": ["Balder", "Heimdall", "Fandral", "Volstagg"]
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "Which character is known for his speed?",
            "answer": "Quicksilver",
            "options": ["Quicksilver", "Mercury", "Speed", "Flash"]
        },
        {
            "id": 51,
            "question": "Who is the mutant with ruby-quartz sunglasses?",
            "answer": "Cyclops",
            "options": ["Cyclops", "Sunfire", "Firestar", "Kree"]
        },
        {
            "id": 52,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Master of Kung Fu'?",
            "answer": "Shang-Chi",
            "options": ["Shang-Chi", "Ares", "Elektra", "Deadpool"]
        },
        {
            "id": 53,
            "question": "Who is the former sidekick of Captain America?",
            "answer": "Bucky Barnes",
            "options": ["Bucky Barnes", "Sam Wilson", "Rick Jones", "Jim Morita"]
        },
        {
            "id": 54,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'God of War'?",
            "answer": "Ares",
            "options": ["Ares", "Hercules", "Zeus", "Thor"]
        },
        {
            "id": 55,
            "question": "Who is the guardian of Knowhere?",
            "answer": "Rocket Raccoon",
            "options": ["Rocket Raccoon", "Groot", "Drax", "Gamora"]
        },
        {
            "id": 56,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Silver Surfer'?",
            "answer": "Silver Surfer",
            "options": ["Silver Surfer", "Nova", "Star-Lord", "Galactus"]
        },
        {
            "id": 57,
            "question": "Who is the mutant with superhuman strength and invulnerability?",
            "answer": "Colossus",
            "options": ["Colossus", "Hulk", "She-Hulk", "Thing"]
        },
        {
            "id": 58,
            "question": "Which character is known as the 'Master Assassin'?",
            "answer": "Elektra",
            "options": ["Elektra", "Black Widow", "Deadpool", "Moon Knight"]
        },
        {
            "id": 59,
            "question": "Who is the mutant with the power to manipulate probability?",
            "answer": "Longshot",
            "options": ["Longshot", "Wolverine", "Cyclops", "Storm"]
        },
        {
            "id": 60,
            "question": "Which character is known for his leadership of the X-Men?",
            "answer": "Professor X",
            "options": ["Professor X", "Magneto", "Iceman", "Beast"]
        }
    ]
}